<?xml version="1.0"?>
<page title="Development">
  <section title="Milestone 2 - Chaos rules">
    <subsection title="What its about?">
      <p>
        Milestone 2 of Feuerkraft should present a fully playable
        game, it might be short and the missions might be simple, but
        beside that it should be fully playable and provide a
        challange for the player. Milestone 2 should also give an
        introduction to the overall story that will be part of
        Feuerkraft. The characters that one will meet in M2 might or
        might not be the same as in M3, this has not yet been decided.
      </p>
    </subsection>

    <subsection title="Planed Features">
      <ul>
        <li>defining of new vehicle/building types/parameters via
        scripts</li>      
        <li>communication/command with/over other troops</li>
        <li>mission recording and replay</li>
        <li>savegame support in the mission (might be limited)</li>
        <li>many different kinds of vehicles with different abilities</li>
        <li>an interesting storyline (well... and maybe not, I am not a writer, but I'll try my best)</li>
        <li>joystick and gamepad support (currently in bad shape)</li>
      </ul>
    </subsection>

    <subsection title="Finished Features">
      <ul>
        <li>level file format is mostly done, serialisation is still
        and issue</li>
        <li>scripting support via Guile with help of Swig is working
          and so far easily extensible if needed</li>
        <li>you can walk around without a vehicle and change the
          vehicle if you like</li>
        <li>OpenGL support is working (via ClanLib0.7)</li>
        <li>map engine is basically working</li>
        <li>some more vehicle types needs to be added</li>
        <li>some kind of ai, pathfind, etc. for computer controlled vehicle is missing</li>
      </ul>
    </subsection>
  </section>

  <section title="Milestone 1 - Drive Demo">
    <p>
      Milestone 1, also known as Drive Demo provides a simple drive
      around on the map, no missions or anything, just simple driving.
      It provides an intro the the lock and feel of Feuerkraft and
      presents a few special effects. It isn't meant as a game, but
      simply as a techdemo. No scripting support is available and no
      multiplayer.
    </p>
  </section>

</page>